José Carlos de Oliveira Júnior

Belo Horizonte/MG - Brazil \$\infty +55 38 99241-0062

\sim josecarlosdeoliveirajr@gmail.com

Introduction and Objetives

Undergraduate student of BS in Computer Science at Federal University of Minas Gerais. Undergraduate Researcher studying Coq proof assistant for formalization and software verification, and subjective logic. Previously Teaching Assistant at Computer Programming class at Federal University of Minas Gerais, Web and Mobile Developer with React Native, Angular.JS, PHP, and Firebase technologies.

Education

Ago. 2015-Current BS in Computer Science, Federal University of Minas Gerais, Belo Horizonte.

Final project: Verifying sorting algorithms correctness with the Coq proof assistant.

Mar. 2012 - Jan. 2015 Computer Technician, Federal Institute of the Northern Minas Gerais, Salinas.

Relevant Experiences

Dec. 2017-Current Undergraduate Researcher, Federal University of Minas Gerais, Belo Horizonte.

Introduction to Coq proof assistant. Advisor: Mário Sergio Alvim.

Studying logic, functional programming, proof techniques, Coq proof assistant and subjective logic.

Mar. 2019-Dec. 2019 Teaching Assistant, Federal University of Minas Gerais, Belo Horizonte.

Computer Programming with Python at Engineering classes.

Sep. 2018 Contestant, ACM ICPC - Brazilian Regionals - First Phase.

Part of the UFMG Coq Intensive team, ranking 130th out of 1156 teams.

Sep. 2017–Feb. 2018 Systems Analyst, BeeStart, Belo Horizonte.

Worked on web and mobile apps for new startups with PHP, Firebase and React Native.

Mar. 2016–Set. 2017 Web Development Intern, Rockett, Belo Horizonte.

Worked on a tool for creation of websites with Angular.JS.

Nov. 2015-July. 2017 Member, UFMG Informática Júnior, Belo Horizonte.

As Human Resources Director, worked in the process of selecting new members.

As Developer, worked in Web and WordPress projects.

Mar. 2014–Jan. 2015 Researcher as Technician Student, Federal Institute of the Northern Minas Gerais, Salinas.

Georeferencing and the internet as tools for dengue mosquito control (Aedes aegypti) in Salinas - MG.

Advisors: Filipe Vieira Santos de Abreu and Patricia de Oliveira Lucas.

Created and maintained a website with data about dengue mosquito traps in two neighborhoods in Salinas over a year.

Relevant Skills

Programming C, C++, Python, Coq, SQL, JavaScript, PHP

Web and Mobile React Native, Angular. JS, CSS and HTML, Firebase

Languages Portuguese: Native English: Intermediate

Projects

Salon React Native and Firebase. Marketplace mobile app for beauty salons.

Mecânico Digital PHP and Firebase. Marketplace web app for repair shops.

Rockett's Site Editor Angular. JS. Added new features, created new templates, and fixed errors.

Links

GitHub https://github.com/joseoliveirajr

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/jcarlosoliveirajr/